<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>Habit...</title>
      <link>https://doctordsp.github.io/45WM_emhabits</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on Habit...</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>Metacognition Habit</title>
    <link>https://doctordsp.github.io/45WM_emhabits/Metacognition-Habit</link>
    <guid>https://doctordsp.github.io/45WM_emhabits/Metacognition-Habit</guid>
    <description>Mental Habit: Metacognitive Thinking in Engineering Education 1. Description and Theoretical Framework Definition and Importance Metacognitive thinking—often referred to as reflection—is the mental habit of being aware of, monitoring, and intentionally improving one’s own thinking and learning processes.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 02:51:39 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Opportunity Habit</title>
    <link>https://doctordsp.github.io/45WM_emhabits/Opportunity-Habit</link>
    <guid>https://doctordsp.github.io/45WM_emhabits/Opportunity-Habit</guid>
    <description>Mental Habit: Opportunity-Oriented Thinking in Engineering Education 1. Description and Theoretical Framework Definition and Importance Opportunity-oriented thinking is a mental habit rooted in the proactive pursuit of potential.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 02:51:28 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Intellectual Humility Habit</title>
    <link>https://doctordsp.github.io/45WM_emhabits/Intellectual-Humility-Habit</link>
    <guid>https://doctordsp.github.io/45WM_emhabits/Intellectual-Humility-Habit</guid>
    <description>Mental Habit: Intellectual Humility in Engineering Education 1. Description and Theoretical Framework Definition and Importance Intellectual humility is a mental habit characterized by the recognition of one’s intellectual limitations and an openness to alternative perspectives.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 02:51:13 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Connections Habit</title>
    <link>https://doctordsp.github.io/45WM_emhabits/Connections-Habit</link>
    <guid>https://doctordsp.github.io/45WM_emhabits/Connections-Habit</guid>
    <description>Mental Habit: Connected Thinking in Engineering Education Connected thinking can become a mental habit. While mental habits are widely recognized as different than mindset, authors have linked mental habits and the development of entrepreneurial mindset.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 02:51:02 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Creating Value Habit</title>
    <link>https://doctordsp.github.io/45WM_emhabits/Creating-Value-Habit</link>
    <guid>https://doctordsp.github.io/45WM_emhabits/Creating-Value-Habit</guid>
    <description>Mental Habit: Value-Creation Thinking in Engineering Education Figure attributed to valohai.com/blog/managing-ai-products/ Try the game to add an INNOVATION force among other ...</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 02:50:43 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Agency Habit</title>
    <link>https://doctordsp.github.io/45WM_emhabits/Agency-Habit</link>
    <guid>https://doctordsp.github.io/45WM_emhabits/Agency-Habit</guid>
    <description>Mental Habit: Action-Orientation and Agency in Engineering Education 1. Description and Theoretical Framework Definition and Importance Action-orientation and agency is a mental habit characterized by a proactive stance toward problem-solving, an internalized locus of control, and the ability to find or create resources to overcome obstacles.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 02:50:27 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Impact Habit</title>
    <link>https://doctordsp.github.io/45WM_emhabits/Impact-Habit</link>
    <guid>https://doctordsp.github.io/45WM_emhabits/Impact-Habit</guid>
    <description>Mental Habit: Impact Thinking in Engineering Education 1. Description and Theoretical Framework Definition and Importance Impact thinking is a mental habit characterized by the ability to anticipate, analyze, and evaluate the potential long-term and multifaceted consequences of engineering decisions and designs.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 02:50:21 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Habits Document</title>
    <link>https://doctordsp.github.io/45WM_emhabits/Habits-Document</link>
    <guid>https://doctordsp.github.io/45WM_emhabits/Habits-Document</guid>
    <description></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 02:49:57 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Curiosity Habit</title>
    <link>https://doctordsp.github.io/45WM_emhabits/Curiosity-Habit</link>
    <guid>https://doctordsp.github.io/45WM_emhabits/Curiosity-Habit</guid>
    <description>Mental Habit: Curiosity in Engineering Education 1. Description and Theoretical Framework Definition and Importance Curiosity is a mental habit characterized by a strong desire to explore, investigate, and learn that drives individuals to ask questions, seek new information, and develop deeper understanding.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 02:48:36 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Welcome to Quartz 4</title>
    <link>https://doctordsp.github.io/45WM_emhabits/</link>
    <guid>https://doctordsp.github.io/45WM_emhabits/</guid>
    <description>EM Stuff Quartz is a fast, batteries-included static-site generator that transforms Markdown content into fully functional websites. Thousands of students, developers, and teachers are already using Quartz to publish personal notes, websites, and digital gardens to the web.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 19:42:13 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>